Hello.
Where are you from?
We talked to you.
I don't remember everyone.
Well, I know.  You come here every day
and say that Russia in
2030, well, it will fall apart.  I am I am We have
already communicated, yes, several times.
Where are you from?   How so
?  Well, guess where I'm from?  You will
break through there now from a certain city.
I know you can do it.   I
can't get through.  Where are you from?
Well, you named it yourself.  What's the point, what should I
say?
I didn't say where you were from.
Well, I'm from Russia.
Well, that's understandable.  On the face.  And the city?
Perm.
Perm.  Cool.  What are you talking about,
Permian?
Yes, about everything.  Depends on who you come across.  About
cars, about music, about traveling, about
books.  And, of course, of course,
there are Ukrainians who love to
talk about politics, just like you, a Ukrainian
who talks about politics and is
financed by the West.  You are paid
money, you said and you say that
Russia will soon fall apart.  Well, that's it
, I remembered you.
[laughter]
We talked for about an hour, you
fairy tale character.  Yes,
we talked several times.  We came across each other several times and
Yes, yes, yes, I remembered.  I remembered that at
first you said this, then sat there, dumbfounded, like:
“Well, yes, yes, I agreed, I remember.”  Okay,
I remembered.  Yeah, well
, my brains have already been washed.  That's it, that's it.
Yes, washed, right?  I remembered everything.   It was
really great talking to you, wasn't it?
Yeah.  Well then, what will you do next?
Well, come on, we can talk.  Look,
since then, when we spoke,
yes, a lot of time has passed.  For example, right
now Ukraine is taking out some
Wildberries, all the oil refineries.
Today Novorossiysk was simply carried out there for
5 hours straight at night, right?  How do you
think Russia can stop
this war now?
M.
How can Russia stop this howl?
No way?
Not at all.  I don't
think anything depends on Russia now.
Well, that's what I mean, specifically about stopping the war
.  I think that the United States of America will most likely
decide this issue
.
Maybe I'm wrong.   Yes.
Well, as for the United States of America, that's all
, Dukhnkorija is talking about that.
Well, I know, yes.  Well, yes, well then there is no way to
stop it.  I don't know that
this will continue, this
will all continue.   I
don’t know what year everything is until and how
everything will be resolved.  How can I
know this?  I'm not big into politics.  I don't
know how it is there, how it is.  I am an ordinary
person.   An
ordinary person.  Why [snorts] do you
come out here to chat?  An ordinary person.
Well, why do people communicate with each
other?  Let's say I have
some kind of goal for communication.  Let's say I
was talking to Belarusians, they were telling me
about their city, how they were doing, and just
where Chelki had gone and traveled.  I'm
talking about traveling, let's say, we're
chatting.  So he went there to Thailand,
there was this, what was it called, resort in Ptuh or
something like
Phuket.
Phuket.  Phuket, yes.  There he told
how he relaxed.  Well, I'm just wondering
why people communicate with each other at all
?  They are transmitting some information,
right?  Well, what kind of information do you want here?
This is,
well, I’m saying, if I get, I get,
let’s say, on people when I travel, like I have
n’t traveled, I want to
travel abroad.  We talked about this topic
, for example.  He talked about his
travel experience.  Something like that
.
I understand, I understand that you are
sitting here, talking specifically about a specific topic,
specifically about politics, and so
on.
And I communicate, well, on different topics.
Fine.  For example, do you think that
the destruction of Wildberries would be critical for Russia
?
No, of course not, of course not.
Of course not.
The destruction of oil refineries
for Russia will be critical for
everyone.
Well, that's how Ukraine puts up with them.
Well, now you already know that there is a
problem with gasoline.
This is a problem, yes.   There are
already kilometer-long queues at gas stations in
big cities.
Portr.  Yes.  Yes.
Well, I don’t know specifically, if you take
people in general, of course, it will be, well,
critical, yes, but I personally don’t have a
car, I walk and
ride a bike.  It's not for me, it's
all the same to you, understand?
It doesn't affect me.  It doesn't
affect me specifically.  The sanctions that
were in the twenty-first,
twenty-second package, or the
seventy-ninth, yes,
even in 179,
148.
Personally, I can say that they had no effect on me
.  Absolutely nothing.  It’s like I
go to work, I go, I earn money, I
spend it on what I want.  That is, I am not dying of
hunger, I am not dying of hunger.
All.
Well, well, you're not dying of hunger.
They say that about mobilization
, well, it occurred to me too.
Well, if, for example, yes, in the fall
after the elections they announce a full
mobilization in order to defeat the evil NATO and
take you away.
So what and what?  So what, how will you feel about this
?   If
they take it, then they take it.  It's my fate, so I mean,
I'm not going to leave the country, I'm
not going to run away from the military registration and enlistment office.  How can I be
cannon fodder?  Well, then I'll be
cannon fodder.
I have this kind of philosophy, this kind of
life, you know, I go to work every day
and every day every syu No,
look, not cannon fodder, but cannon fodder.
Well, for you, for someone, for us, it
was released for you.  I didn't insult you, though
.
I don't insult either.  I'm not insulting.  I'm just
saying how we perceive you.
This is not meat.
Just bags with
Well, look, the bag breathes, loves,
empathizes with other people.
Yes, he is a breathing, empathetic, loving
bag with this does not apply to you,
Ukrainians, but simply there
we do not care.
Well, we're looking at you.  We are looking at you
.  As for the bags with
you, then, it’s no better.  I don't know,
neither better nor worse.  We are bad, right?  We are
bad and that's it.  We are bad, yes.  We look at you
like you're sacks.  You can
file a complaint with him, you can make a broadcast there about
how bad we are, we don’t care.
Well
, I see you still don't take
that tea bag out of the glass when
you brew tea.
You are very observant.
I've been brewing it since the last meeting.  I was just
waiting for this moment.  This mug
stood for about six months and waited for
our meeting, or rather.  So the stars
have aligned now.  Can you imagine?
Last time you still had a spoon
there.
Listen, I sold it, this little spoon,
to pay my rent for the month,
so that I could last another month in
this country.  Do you understand?
Well, I mean, [ __ ], you see, we've
already taught you to take the spoon out when you drink.  Well, by
next time you'll learn
to take out the bag.
And in winter everything will be really bad.
The heating will be turned off, there will be no gas, and
all our toilets will freeze, and we’ll
probably have to throw food out the window.
No, not in Perm, you won’t freeze in Perm
.  There will be the Moscow region,
Moscow and St. Petersburg so that it freezes out,
because Perm is strategically...
Thank God, I live there, thank God.
Look, everything went around again, and again Yes, I did
.  So you got by. Simply put, there
will be problems with gasoline, but you won’t freeze
.  Moscow will freeze.   Yes.
By the way, I travel around the city by trolleybus.  Well, it seems to be
electricity for now.  I hope there is still
internet access.
Everything is fine for now, we're holding out
until 2000. We'll
have to wait until 2030, and then everything will
fall apart anyway, and that's it, we'll
live wonderfully.  Well, either someone
will capture us there, you or the Americans, or
someone else there.  All.  And then we will live.
For what?  Why would anyone want to capture you?
Who needs you?
No, well, something like Eurasia 2030 and
some other things.
So, this won't capture you.  You
will fall apart Kidryunifeni.  Well, well,
anyway, the Russians will probably still survive at least
one Russian by 2030.  I hope it
will be me.  And I will survive, I guess.  That's how it is
, I think.  That's how
you might survive, right?
Maybe so.
As they say, you know, these worms,
rats, like cockroaches, you know, we'll crawl in there
.
Well, in general, they are tenacious, yes, all kinds of worms,
cockroaches, yes, all kinds of crap are very
tenacious, yes, tenacious.  They're beating us, beating us,
and beating the oil refinery, and Varista, oh my God, I'm
not right now... Oh, by the way, I ordered
something today.  I ordered some clothes from Valberis today
.  Yes.
And it will even arrive in 3 days.
Show the order.  Show
the order on your phone.  I'll show you my phone now
.  What?
See, you're a star.
Well,
well, good.  Well, yes.  Otherwise, we're walking around in rags
, damn it.  Now is the time to stock up.   We
need to prepare bast shoes for the winter and
felt boots too, so as not to
freeze.
Otherwise, who knows.  And you need to
stock up on vodka, stock up on boxes,
stock up on pantries.
There you see, look.  Uh, since last time,
yes, you completely faded out then and now
all you can do is turn everything into a
joke.
This is not a joke, why should I look, you
see, you no longer have any arguments.  You are
completely depressed, completely
down.  Please add:
psychologically depressed, morally
depressed, testosterone dropped, sort of gets up.   Yes.   Yes.
And the beard doesn't grow.  I have to, [ __ ], you
know, it's like a facial hair transplant
.
And your fingers look feminine.
My fingers are feminine, yes, they are thin and
pale, because the sun
never rises over Russia.  Well, we have a minus. That
is, look, come on, let's do it this way, let's
summarize it this way.  Last time, yes, you
were so cheeky, Russia and everything there, and
then you cried, yes, about migrants and how
everything was there.  You and I, I remember our
conversation, I remember, I remember it completely, yes.  At
first it was so childish, and then it died down
, in short, and about the migrants, yes,
we have these Tajiks and that’s all.  Islam, in short,
whined and whined, and then sat there completely extinguished,
right?  And now you see that all you can do is
joke, like we have unidoses there,
the sun, and so on.  That's it, see?  But you,
look, we have civilized you, right?  You've
already started taking out the uh spoon, right?
Soon you'll start taking out the, uh, bag, and
then maybe you'll stop being there and say
that you're from Perm.  Okay, let's
go today.  Subscribe to our WhatsApp
channel, here is the QR code.  The same news is posted there
as in the
Telegram channel.  For those who don't have
Telegram or who don't use it for
other reasons.  Subscribe to our
WhatsApp channel.